level1_questions = [
    {'question': 'What is the national animal of India?',
    'choices': ['Lion', 'Tiger', 'Wolf', 'Elephant'],
    'answer': 2},

    {'question': 'Sachin Tendulkar played which sports?',
    'choices': ['Hockey', 'Kabaddi', 'Cricket', 'Football'],
    'answer': 3},

     {'question': 'What is 20-10*3 equal to?',
      'choices': ['-10', '30', '10', '40'],
      'answer': 1},

    {'question': "What is India's national aquatic animal?",
      'choices': ['Crocodile', 'River Dolphin', 'Katla Fish', 'Green Frog'],
      'answer': 2},

     {'question': 'Which city is called as Silicon Valley of India?',
      'choices': ['Hyderabad', 'Chennai', 'Bangalore', 'Pune'],
      'answer': 3},

     {'question': 'Which state has Taj Mahal?',
      'choices': ['Uttar Pradesh', 'Agra', 'Gujarat', 'Ahmedabad'],
      'answer': 1}

     ]

#Level 2 questions
level2_questions = [{'question': 'lv2 5+3',
              'choices': ['5', '8', '3', '4'],
              'answer': 2},
             {'question': 'lv2 6*3',
              'choices': ['8', '88', '18', '28'],
              'answer': 3},
             {'question': 'lv2 10*3',
              'choices': ['30', '40', '20', '90'],
              'answer': 1},
            {'question': 'lv2 5+3',
              'choices': ['5', '8', '3', '4'],
              'answer': 2},
             {'question': 'lv2 6*3',
              'choices': ['8', '88', '18', '28'],
              'answer': 3},
             {'question': 'lv2 10*3',
              'choices': ['30', '40', '20', '90'],
              'answer': 1}
             ]

#Level 3 questions
level3_questions = [{'question': 'lv3 5+3',
              'choices': ['5', '8', '3', '4'],
              'answer': 2},
             {'question': 'lv3 6*3',
              'choices': ['8', '88', '18', '28'],
              'answer': 3},
             {'question': 'lv3 10*3',
              'choices': ['30', '40', '20', '90'],
              'answer': 1},
            {'question': 'lv3 5+3',
              'choices': ['5', '8', '3', '4'],
              'answer': 2},
             {'question': 'lv3 6*3',
              'choices': ['8', '88', '18', '28'],
              'answer': 3},
             {'question': 'lv3 10*3',
              'choices': ['30', '40', '20', '90'],
              'answer': 1}
             ]